Piyush Atghara



piyushatghara@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/piyush-atghara



7978024043



https://github.com/crypto-bot7

Summary

I work with the Business teams to analyze automation opportunities, develop processes / bots / scripts, test and deploy into production.

Develop Quick Process Automation (QPAs) to automate complex processes which reduces efforts in repetitive manual task for the client. Prepare PDD and SDD for documentation.

Have Demonstrated Web Development experience using Modern JavaScript Frameworks (Angular 4).

Technical Skills:

Languages - Python, PowerShell Scripting, VB .Net, Excel VBA, JavaScript, HTML

Python Libraries - Requests, Zeep, logging, scrapy, xml.sax, smtplib, urllib3

API & Data Formats - REST, SOAP, XML, JSON

IDEs - Visual Studio Code, Eclipse, PowerShell ISE

Tools - Putty, SOAP UI, Postman, Wireshark, Fiddler, Task Scheduler

Technologies and Frameworks - UiPath, AssistEdge, Angular 4

Database - Oracle 11, MYSQL, MS SQL

OS - MS Windows Server, Cisco IOS, MS SQL Server

Knowledge of:

Ticketing - Service Now, Jira

Data Visualization - Kibana

Infrastructure Technologies - Cisco routers & switches, Cisco Call Manager (CUCM), MS Teams.

Monitoring Tool - New Relic, Big Panda

Experience

Systems Engineer

Infosys

Jul 2019 - Present (1 year 10 months +)

Working with one of the largest microprocessor manufactures:

- Reduced the time taken in a business process from 'weeks' to 'days' (70 80% Reduction) by leveraging RPA, PowerShell scripts and Excel Macros (VBA) for client.
- Identified opportunities to automate manual tasks using Robotics Process Automation technology.

Notable project - Automation of Comprehensive Hygiene Check Process for Cisco call manager pbx. Used web services (SOAP API) over python soap client to automate the end to end process and trigger indicative mails written in HTML.

Implemented logging and caching functionality in the python code as well.

System Engineer Trainee

Infosys

Feb 2019 - Jun 2019 (5 months)

Developed Single Page Web Application: "Performance Management Dashboard for Network Devices" using Angular, REST API, Java, Hibernate, Oracle DB

Executive - Credit Operations, Consumer Branch Credit & Operations

Bajaj Finserv May 2018 - Jan 2019 (9 months)

Education

C V Raman Global University (est. CVRCE), Bhubaneswar

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Mechanical Engineering 2013 - 2017

Vikash Residential School

10+2, science 2011 - 2013

Licenses & Certifications

Step into Robotic Process Automation - GUVI Geek Networks 90Zf7e5Lm1r0541M8X

Java(Basic) - HackerRank

Infosys Certified IOT Professional - Infosys

AssistEdge RPA Developer Certification - EdgeVerve

Issued Mar 2021 - Expires Mar 2023 AERPADC202103230101

Skills

Robotic Process Automation (RPA) • Powershell Scripting • Python scripting • Project Management • UiPath • Angular • Microsoft SQL Server • SOAP • REST APIs • AssistEdge

Honors & Awards

Insta Award - Infosys

Dec 2020

For handling complex product issues and taking responsibility for automation.